A Finding Aid to the Holger Cahill Papers, 1910-1993, bulk 1910-1960, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Works Progress Administration Federal Art Project, 1934-1970; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 10.75 Linear feet Boxes 2-14, 18, MMs009
  - Other New Deal Art Projects, 1935-1942; 3.11; Archival Resource Key
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 11, September 1936-February 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0777-0795)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 12, February 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0796-0812)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 13, March-June 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0813-0829)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 14, July 1937-January 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0830-0862)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 15, March 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0863-0873)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 16, circa April-August 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0874-0881)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 17, September 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0882-0898)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 18, February 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0899-0918)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 19, June 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0919-0948)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 20, November 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0949-0965)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 21, March 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0966-0981)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 22, September 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0982-1003)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 23, March 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1004-1010)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 24, May 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1011-1016)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 8 (duplicate), January-February 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1070-1105)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 10 (duplicate), June-August 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1106-1125)
  - Publicity and Printed Material, 1934-1944, 1961; 3.12; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains printed material relating to the WPA/FAP as well as material used for publicity including transcripts of lectures and essays (some with hand-written notations), news clippings, press releases, and publications. For additional material of this type see Series 4: Writings, Lectures and Speeches and Series 8: Printed Material. Additional press releases can be found in 3.13: Scrapbooks.
    - Brochure, Purposes, Functions, Techniques: Federal Art Project Exhibitions, undated; Archival Resource Key; (see MMs009) (Reel 3482, Frame 1134-1153)
    - Government Acts and Resolutions, 1935-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0341-0373)
    - Government Acts and Resolutions, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0255-0437)
    - Lectures and Essays, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0520-0531)
    - Lectures and Essays, 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 0942-1070)
    - Lectures and Essays, 1937; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0494-0503)
    - Lectures and Essays, 1937; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0602-0605)
    - Lectures and Essays, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0509-0519)
    - Lectures and Essays, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0616-0632)
    - Lectures and Essays, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0638-0644)
    - List of Magazine Articles on FAP, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0789-0798)
    - Press Releases, 1936-1939, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 1071-1101)
    - Press Releases, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0633-0637)
    - Press Releases, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0655-0656)
    - News Clippings, undated; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 4) (Reel 1108, Frame 1108-1124)
    - News Clippings, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 4) (Reel 1108, Frame 1318)
    - News Clippings, undated; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 4) (Reel 1108, Frame 1320-1324)
    - News Clippings, undated; Archival Resource Key; (4 of 4) (Reel 1108, Frame 1327-1332)
    - News Clippings, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 1316-1317)
    - News Clippings, 1935; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 1126-1149)
    - News Clippings, 1935; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 1333-1337)
    - News Clippings, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 1150-1231)
    - News Clippings, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 1338-1367)
    - News Clippings, 1937; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2; see also Box 18) (Reel 1108, Frame 1232-1257)
    - News Clippings, 1937; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2; see also Box 18) (Reel 1108, Frame 1368-1401)
    - News Clippings, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 1258-1277)
    - News Clippings, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 1319)
    - News Clippings, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel 1109, Frame 0001-0107)
    - News Clippings, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 1278-1294)
    - News Clippings, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 1325-1326)
    - News Clippings, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel 1109, Frame 0108-0156)
    - News Clippings, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 1295)
    - News Clippings, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 1296-1314)
    - News Clippings, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0157-0158)
    - News Clippings, 1939-1943, 1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0995-1030)
    - Publications, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0160-0254)
    - Publications, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0438-0473)
    - Publications, 1940; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1109, Frame 0474-0598)
    - Publications, 1940; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1109, Frame 0683-0737)
    - Publications, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0738-0963)
    - Publications, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0964-1012)
    - Sunday Night Art Forum Announcements, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 1102-1107)
    - WPA Technical Problems of the Artist Series, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5296, Frame 0747-0811)
    - WPA Technical Series, 1940, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 0599-0682)
    - WPA Technical Series, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5296, Frame 0817-0862)
  - Scrapbooks, 1936-1939; 3.13; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains three scrapbooks: Scrapbook I contains primarily press releases from the WPA Works Program as well as state progress reports, exhibition catalogs, and miscellaneous printed material. It includes photos of sculptor Jose Ruiz de Rivera and a New York Cityscape by Berenice Abbott. Scrapbook II contains news clippings and printed material concerning FAP conferences and the Index of American Design. Scrapbook III contains news clippings, exhibition catalogs and miscellaneous printed material. It also conains six photos of art centers and exhibitions, six photos of art classes and seven photos of artwork.
    - Scrapbook I, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 1466-1494)
    - Scrapbook I, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0005-0024)
    - Scrapbook I, January-May 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0025-0061)
    - Scrapbook I, June 1-15, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0062-0092)
    - Scrapbook I, June 16-30, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0093-0129)
    - Scrapbook I, July 1-15, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0130-0152)
    - Scrapbook I, July 16-31, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0153-0184)
    - Scrapbook I, August 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0185-0218)
    - Scrapbook I, September 1-15, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0219-0233)
    - Scrapbook I, September 16-30, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0234-0262)
    - Scrapbook I, October 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0263-0302)
    - Scrapbook I, November 1-10, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0303-0338)
    - Scrapbook I, November 11-19, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0340-0364)
    - Scrapbook I, November 20-30, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0365-0383)
    - Scrapbook I, December 1-8, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0384-0412)
    - Scrapbook I, December 9-21, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0413-0434)
    - Scrapbook I, December 22-31, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0435-0461)
    - Scrapbook I, January 1-12, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0462-0493)
    - Scrapbook I, January 13-18, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0494-0520)
    - Scrapbook I, January 19-27, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0521-0559)
    - Scrapbook I, January 28-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0560-0587)
    - Scrapbook I, February 1-15, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0588-0642)
    - Scrapbook I, February 16-28, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0643-0683)
    - Scrapbook I, March 1-10, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0684-0723)
    - Scrapbook I, March 11-23, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0724-0772)
    - Scrapbook I, March 25-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0773-0801)
    - Scrapbook I, April 1-21, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0802-0844)
    - Scrapbook I, April 22-30, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0845-0882)
    - Scrapbook I, May 1-10, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0883-0921)
    - Scrapbook I, May 11-16, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0922-0956)
    - Scrapbook I, May 17-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0957-0993)
    - Scrapbook I, June 1-15, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 0994-1024)
    - Scrapbook I, June 16-30, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1025-1056)
    - Scrapbook I, July 1-18, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1057-1113)
    - Scrapbook I, July 19-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1114-1146)
    - Scrapbook I, August 1-10, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1147-1177)
    - Scrapbook I, August 11-20, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1178-1219)
    - Scrapbook I, August 21-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1220-1247)
    - Scrapbook I, September 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1248-1315)
    - Scrapbook I, October 1-21, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1316-1346)
    - Scrapbook I, October 22-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1347-1370)
    - Scrapbook I, November 1-10, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1371-1405)
    - Scrapbook I, November 14-20, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1406-1425)
    - Scrapbook I, November 21-30, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1426-1453)
    - Scrapbook I, December 1-14, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1454-1500)
    - Scrapbook I, December 15-31, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5293, Frame 1501-1541)
    - Scrapbook I, January 1-15, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0004-0030)
    - Scrapbook I, January 16-24, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0031-0056)
    - Scrapbook I, January 25-31, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0057-0093)
    - Scrapbook I, February 1-15, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0094-0132)
    - Scrapbook I, February 16-28, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0133-0170)
    - Scrapbook I, March 1-14, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0171-0195)
    - Scrapbook I, March 15-21, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0196-0222)
    - Scrapbook I, March 22-31, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0223-0249)
    - Scrapbook I, March-April 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0250-0291)
    - Scrapbook I, April 1-11, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0292-0326)
    - Scrapbook I, April 12-30, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0327-0357)
    - Scrapbook I, May 1-14, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0358-0396)
    - Scrapbook I, May 15-21, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0397-0427)
    - Scrapbook I, May 22-31, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0428-0469)
    - Scrapbook I, June 1-12, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0470-0494)
    - Scrapbook I, June 13-30, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0495-0534)
    - Scrapbook I, July 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0535-0565)
    - Scrapbook II, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5294, Frame 0566-0638)
    - Scrapbook III, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key; (see Box 18) (Reel 5294, Frame 0639-0787)
  - Photographs, circa 1935-1948; 3.14; Archival Resource Key
    This series begins with photographs of WPA artists, regional directors, and art administrators. The individuals pictured include: Lucienne Bloch, Karl Knaths, Donald J. Bear, Max Spivak, Increase Robinson, F. C. Harrington, Russell C. Parr, George G. Thorp, Eve Alsman Fuller, R. Bruce Inverarity, Eleanor Roosevelt with R. Bruce Inverarity, Florence Kerr, Robert Armstrong Andrews, Richard C. Morrison, Jacob Baker, Holger Cahill and Jacob Baker, Joseph Danysh, C. Adolph Glassgold, Thomas C. Parker, Elizabeth Olds, Milton Horn, Juan Sanchez, Patricino Barela, Sam Brown, Harry Hopkins and Holger Cahill, Stanton MacDonald Wright at the dedication of the Father Garces monument, John Palo-Kangas, Seminole Indians at the opening of the Miami Federal Galleries, Ellen Woodward with Thomas C. Parker, and Holger Cahill with Duncan Phillips and Harry L. Hopkins.
    Also found here are three photograph "albums." Photograph Album I contains photos of artwork, installations, and Shaker furniture and buildings. Photograph Album II contains photos of artists, art classes, and artwork in addition to printed material. Photograph Album III contains photos of posters and murals, group activities and classes relating to the WPA and defense.
    This series also contains thirteen photographs of "Changing New York" by Berenice Abbott. The remainder of the series consists of FAP photos of art classes, gallery installations, state art centers and staff and artwork, arranged by state.
    For additional FAP photographs see 3.1 (for photographs of FAP administrators), 3.2. (for photographs of Artists), 3.8 (for photographs related to the Index of American Design), 3.10 (for photographs from the 1939-1940 World's Fair) and 3.13 (for photographs from FAP scrapbooks).
    - Adminstrator Photos, circa 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key; (includes photograph of Eleanor Roosevelt, 3/25/38) (Reel 1109, Frame 1126-1144)
    - Artist, Regional Director, and Art Administrator Photos, circa 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1147-1197)
    - Berenice Abbott Photos, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1198-1224)
    - Berenice Abbott, Negatives and Copy Prints, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Photograph Album I, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5296, Frame 1021-1354)
    - Photograph Album I, cont., circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5297, Frame 0004-0331)
    - Photograph Album II, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key; (see Box 18) (Reel 5297, Frame 0332-0418)
    - Photograph Album III, circa 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5297, Frame 0419-0478)
    - Alabama Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1109, Frame 1225-1231)
    - Alabama Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0481-0484)
    - Arizona Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1109, Frame 1232-1251)
    - Arizona Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0486-0554)
    - California Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1109, Frame 1252-1337)
    - California Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0556-0741)
      (includes photos of Benianino Bufano, Donal Hord and John Palo-Kangas)
    - Colorado Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1109, Frame 1338-1354)
    - Colorado Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0743-0760)
    - Connecticut Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5297, Frame 0762-0763)
    - District of Columbia Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0406-0428)
    - District of Columbia Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0765-0787)
    - Florida Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0001-0079)
    - Florida Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0789-0919)
    - Idaho, Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5297, Frame 0921-0930)
    - Illinois Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0080-0161)
    - Illinois, Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5297, Frame 0932-1268)
      (includes photographs of Edward Millman and Mitchell Siporin)
    - Indiana Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5297, Frame 1270)
    - Iowa Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel 1110, Frame 0162-0163)
    - Iowa Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel 5297, Frame 1272-1344)
    - Iowa Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel 5298, Frame 0005-0023)
    - Kansas Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5298, Frame 0025-0033)
    - Louisiana Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5298, Frame 0035-0042)
    - Maine Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5298, Frame 44)
    - Maryland Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1110, Frame 0164-0165)
    - Massachusetts Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0166-0236)
    - Massachusetts Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5298, Frame 0046-0189)
    - Michigan Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0237-0284)
    - Michigan Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5298, Frame 0191-0234)
      (includes photos of Samuel Cashwan and Walt Speck)
    - Minnesota Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0285-0289)
    - Minnesota Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5298, Frame 0236-0339)
      (includes photo of Gov. Harold E. Stassen)
    - Mississippi Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0290-0301)
    - Mississippi Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5298, Frame 0341-0354)
    - Missouri Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5298, Frame 0356-0357)
    - Montana Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5298, Frame 0359-0378)
    - New Mexico Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0302-0311)
    - New Mexico Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5298, Frame 0380-0497)
      (includes photo of Patrocino Barela)
    - New York Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel 1110, Frame 0454-0647)
    - New York Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel 5298, Frame 0499-1357)
      (includes photos of Arshile Gorky, Edward Laning, Eric Mose and James Michael Newell)
    - New York Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel 5299, Frame 0004-0360)
    - North Carolina Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0312-0327)
    - North Carolina Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0362-0596)
      (includes photo of Ambassador Josephus Daniels and Robert Vose)
    - Ohio Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 328)
    - Ohio Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0598-0625)
    - Oklahoma Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0329-0338)
    - Oklahoma Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0627-0670)
    - Oregon Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0339-0346)
    - Oregon Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0672-0779)
      (includes photo of Louis Bunce)
    - Pennsylvania Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0347-0350)
    - Pennsylvania Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0781-0819)
    - Rhode Island Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0351-0356)
    - Rhode Island Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0821-0830)
    - South Carolina Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5299, Frame 0832-0833)
    - Tennessee Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5299, Frame 0835-0842)
    - Utah Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0357-0366)
    - Utah Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0844-0887)
    - Virginia Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0367-0405)
    - Virginia Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0889-0946)
    - Washington Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0429-0433)
      (includes photo of Eleanor Roosevelt, 1938)
    - Washington Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 0948-1001)
    - Washington Photographs? (state not identified), circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1110, Frame 0434-0435)
    - West Virginia Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5299, Frame 1003-1022)
    - Wisconsin Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0436-0449)
    - Wisconsin Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 1024-1062)
    - Wyoming Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1110, Frame 0450-0453)
    - Wyoming Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5299, Frame 1064-1082)
    - Unidentified Locations Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1110, Frame 0648-0677)
    - Miscellaneous Center Projects and Artwork Photographs, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5299, Frame 1084-1125)
      (includes photo of Reuben Nakian)
- Writings, Lectures and Speeches, 1916-1960; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Boxes 14-15, 18
  This series contains typescripts of writings, lectures and speeches by Cahill and others. A large portion of the material relates to the WPA FAP, but there are also book and exhibition reviews and other works of art criticism by Cahill. For additional copies of writings by Cahill see Series 8: Printed Material.
  The series is arranged into five subseries:
  4.1: Lectures and Speeches by Cahill, 1930-1945
  4.2: Lectures and Speeches by Others, 1916-1940
  4.3: Writings by Cahill, 1928-1960
  4.4: Writings by Others, 1932-1957